<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hugo Bootstrap</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Hugo Bootstrap</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year} Daniel Jackson. All Rights Reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 23:47:16 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Full Self Driving Review</title><link>/posts/fsd-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 23:47:16 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/fsd-first-impressions/</guid><description>On a non-stop 15 hour trip, I drove from Portland, Oregon, to Los Angeles, California, in a recently purchased Tesla model 3. The journey was nearly 1,000 miles long and was piloted almost exclusively by the Full Self Driving (FSD) system. It effortlessly handled standard highway situations, keeping a safe distance from the car in front and overtaking traffic automatically when needed. I intervened four times to address unsafe conditions that, in retrospect, the car would have dealt with sufficiently. With those exceptions, the most work I had to do was navigate off highways to reach superchargers. Overall, it was a fantastic drive where I could pay attention to the road while relaxing, which, oddly enough, allowed me to stay alert despite such a long drive.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>Hello There Hi, my name is Daniel Jackson. I live in New York and am a software engineer by trade. This blog is a fun and constructive way to get my thoughts in order and reinforce what I have and am learning.
Since this is for self-betterment and not self-advertisement, I&amp;rsquo;ll keep this short. I studied Computer Science and Applied Math Economics which is what most posts will be on. I&amp;rsquo;ve found that the most effective way to become fluent in a subject is to learn the theory through application.</description></item><item><title>Offline</title><link>/offline/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/offline/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>