<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Hugo Bootstrap</title><link>/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Hugo Bootstrap</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year} Daniel Jackson. All Rights Reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 23:47:16 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Full Self Driving Review</title><link>/posts/fsd-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 23:47:16 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/fsd-first-impressions/</guid><description>On a non-stop 15 hour trip, I drove from Portland, Oregon, to Los Angeles, California, in a recently purchased Tesla model 3. The journey was nearly 1,000 miles long and was piloted almost exclusively by the Full Self Driving (FSD) system. It effortlessly handled standard highway situations, keeping a safe distance from the car in front and overtaking traffic automatically when needed. I intervened four times to address unsafe conditions that, in retrospect, the car would have dealt with sufficiently. With those exceptions, the most work I had to do was navigate off highways to reach superchargers. Overall, it was a fantastic drive where I could pay attention to the road while relaxing, which, oddly enough, allowed me to stay alert despite such a long drive.</description></item><item><title>The Sicilian Defense</title><link>/posts/sicilian-defense/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:54:11 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/sicilian-defense/</guid><description>Template Intro: The basic Sicilian (1. e4, c5) The basic idea is to hit d4 to prevent white from playing d4 and controlling the center Common Variations Look up most common responses after c5 Open Sicilian: Played X% of the time After 1. White brings the king&amp;rsquo;s knight out and then push the d4 pawn. The trade will put white&amp;rsquo;s knight in the center The general goal for white is to allow for rapid development Closed Sicilian: Played X % of the time Dragon French (me!</description></item></channel></rss>